Despite a weak global cues,
you saw how good our performance was yesterday.
After that, we have come close to that level
where the market can act as an important resistance.
Also,
more than half of the short covering that happened yesterday happened, so
in such a situation, our expiry is ahead,
hence many things can be settled for you. If we
talk about these options and hourly duty,
then we need to be a little happy with our hands.
If we talk about
Lipstick, which is an important level, if it is
above 80 then it is a good thing or
we can say that it is a strong rose. If
we talk about all the markets at this time,
we are seeing it in the neutral to give correct mark. If we are tightening it, then we can
talk about the support levels visible only above SGX Nifty, then around the same level. First of all, the first
support that is visible is
70075 and after that there will be a major level of 60.
After this, if we talk about crude oil, but you
will see that it is also in the review of a question, there is also
more in Batham Natural Gas.  Near
6060, there is a continuous rise in natural gas.
Silver
is flat and gold is
seen to be trading. Just by
looking at the currency market, you will see that it is
around 70070 and has been continuously trading after that,
therefore, around this level, if
we
talk about address collection, this knowledge, after two days of
buying, there is a heavy selling, a heavy
profit booking, see tomorrow
from the side of the fans, you will be able to see it here. Also, if we talk about immediate, then it is a
good thing,
if we talk about NET, the penis was released from it, but the
data is not that big, so there is a
small number on the side of the penis, it becomes important for us to look at it.
If we talk about castor oil,
after this, there is
maximum news in the newspaper today. The first
news that came out on Airtel, what is
Reliance Mutual Fund Quote, I
like and share it here and
keep 204 point five house near it, it is 212  A
bulk deal has been done. First of all, the first news is
on Airtel. On the other hand, news has come out on
Airtel.
After Bharti Airtel, the green telecom operator has done it
after the inspection of the equipment maker.
Whatever they have to say, where did the free India Gift
5G network trial stop? So,
from here, the focus of the company is on Airtel.
Then all the platforms of June, all the
focus is on fabricated trials.
Earlier, we had seen that some time
ago, it was controlled in Bengaluru also,
focusing on rural locations. In this way, it becomes a
good thing for the company.
Next, if we talk about the
jackfruit tree that has come out of the city, the news is that the
drug is from set, from whom has it got
promotion from the Indian Drug
Regulator and for what thing, for
conducting free trials for their medicine,
whose name is Kuber, given to Jat,
then they have got permission for its factory. The
next news is that after returning from there,
yesterday also they tried to cover it that in this there is
a big trap.
Whatever you have, they have less than the statue
and are going to fruition, then you will be
able to see here that they are restless or have held 121 crore 725 likes plus
equity shares, the day has seen them
multiple the price of around 150 on BSE. Next 9
news regarding nickel carrier IG Petrochemicals,
what has happened in this that
if we talk about board has held
151 likes, G Kishore has advertised bikes
according to 98100, this has also been appealed and
here
after that if we talk about cotton, the numbers have
started coming, before that the
commentary of the management has been the chairman, then
we also see the time of pilots, so in
such a situation
we will talk about Godrej Consumer Products, so what do they have to
say from here, the comments coming out,
expect to deliver high single duty
six growth, so I am telling about quick recovery, the company is telling
here, the commentary is coming out
and the [ __ ] should be held based system,
how impressive are most of the numbers from July to October quarter, so
important news to cover live
Tried for this, such Tuesday,
April 20, for this you can subscribe to the channel,
you will find all the important things
in the description, if you
can click on the educational close button,
you will get it on the channel, thank you so much.